<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Niko Ruiz</title>
    <link>https://nikoruiz.co/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Niko Ruiz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 21:56:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nikoruiz.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving Pickathon Project</title>
      <link>https://nikoruiz.co/posts/my-second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 21:56:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nikoruiz.co/posts/my-second-post/</guid>
      <description>I am currently working on improving and translating my C++ 1050 Led and Kinect project onto a Rust platform. The Pickathon program was a huge success we ran it longer than intended and our display drew way more intention than I ever expected. Now I want to optimize it so that it can run efficiently on a Raspberry Pi. Instead of taking pixels from an OpenGl image, I will be directly taking the pixels out of the RGB data from the depth sensor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1050 leds and an Xbox Kinect</title>
      <link>https://nikoruiz.co/projects/led_kinnect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 13:44:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nikoruiz.co/projects/led_kinnect/</guid>
      <description>Intro Back in May 2018 my web developer pal Dan Wright, roped me into collaborating with him on an art installation at Pickathon 2018. His original concept for the interactive project was to use the flaschen taschen project, and build a giant Etch-a-Sketch that would be operated by two people. After a few morning coffee sessions in our living room the project evolved into a light display that would use Xbox Kinect it depth sensor to project human movement even in pitch black darkeness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Page</title>
      <link>https://nikoruiz.co/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 14:30:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nikoruiz.co/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my custom one stop shop to find out all of the latest and greatest of my program happenings and maybe get to know me a little bit along the way. Drop me a line at any time if you have questions or if you just want to say “hi”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>