<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Niko Ruiz</title>
    <link>https://nikoruiz.co/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Niko Ruiz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 21:56:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nikoruiz.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving Pickathon Project</title>
      <link>https://nikoruiz.co/posts/my-second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 21:56:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nikoruiz.co/posts/my-second-post/</guid>
      <description>Currently working on improving and translating my C++ 1050 Led and Kinect project into a rust project. I want to optimize it so that it can run efficiently on a Raspberry Pi. Instead of taking pixels from an OpenGl image, I will be directly taking the pixels out of the RGB data from the depth sensor. Will be make the openGl window an option that one can still use if they wish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1050 leds and an Xbox Kinnect</title>
      <link>https://nikoruiz.co/projects/led_kinnect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 13:44:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nikoruiz.co/projects/led_kinnect/</guid>
      <description>Intro In May my current housemate, Dan Wright, told me about how he got approved for an art installation at Pickathon 2018. The original concept of the interactive project was to use the flaschen taschen project, and build a Etch-a-Sketch that would be operated by two people. After a few morning coffee sessions in our living room the idea of connecting a Xbox Kinnect to the display came up. I took the challenge of getting the data from the Kinect to display on the LED display.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Page</title>
      <link>https://nikoruiz.co/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 14:30:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nikoruiz.co/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>I have created this site to let one know a bit about myself at a personal and technical level. I also wanted to have my collection of my work in one location for easy navigation, along with a detailed history of the project. Please feel welcome to message me if you have any questions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>